So I'm continuing ripping my paper, and one, you know, this is why I like tearing my paper down.
You can almost see how this is sort of like, you know, as I'm working the coolest thing to me about being an artist, you know working, is that you get ideas.
You know I'm looking at the way I'm tearing this paper down and it's like a book already, and I'm like what kind of book can I make today with cyanotypes, and one thing that I forgot to mention is that the cyanotype is cheap.
I mean one of the few materials that I work with that is dirt cheap.
Paper is not that cheap when you use a lot of it, but the material itself is.
So again I'm back to kind of daydreaming about my little book here.
I'm going to keep ripping.
So again I've got another quarter sheet, and this is where this is kind of cool too because I can think about what size prints I want to make.
I'm not buying this paper pre-ripped.
You know, thinking in my little crazy head here like oh I can make a print that is this long or I can make a print that is this big.
So I'm going to save these two and I'm going to cut these down.
You know some days I like big prints.
Some days I like small prints.
But what I'm going to start coating are just a couple of small sheets to show just how to coat and how to work with the material.
One interesting thing about what's going on here today is it's a very humid day here in Austin, Texas and this paper is already, it's sucking up the humidity.
I can almost feel it curl right now.
That's one thing about print making to me.
It's just so hands on that you really start to notice things.